<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>COMP2043 GRP Group 10 Open Educational Resources :: GRP G10 OER</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/index.html</link>
    <description>In the forefront of today’s film and television Production, Virtual Production is gradually becoming a key force to promote industry change. Virtual production is an innovative film and television production technology, which deeply integrates traditional film and television shooting with advanced digital technology. Through real-time rendering, motion capture and other technical means, realistic scenes, characters and special effects are created in the virtual environment, and can be presented in real time on the shooting scene, so that creators can adjust and optimize the shooting content in real time. Greatly improve the flexibility and efficiency of creation.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:52:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10: Scheduling Meetings Effectively</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/10.scheduling/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:52:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/10.scheduling/index.html</guid>
      <description>Ensuring that meetings are scheduled efficiently is a crucial aspect of successful stakeholder engagement. This becomes especially important when stakeholders have demanding schedules. Striking a balance between minimizing disruptions and securing a suitable time slot is key. Our team encountered several challenges in scheduling meetings with stakeholders, leading to delays and inefficiencies. By sharing our experiences, we hope to provide a structured guide for scheduling meetings effectively.&#xA;Recommended Tool for Scheduling: Doodle Our stakeholders initially suggested using Doodle as a scheduling tool. After using it, we found it to be highly effective in streamlining the scheduling process. Doodle allows users to create a form with multiple time slots, which can be shared with stakeholders via a link. Stakeholders can then easily select their available time slots, simplifying the coordination process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9: Effective Stakeholder Meetings: Lessons from a Collaborative Project</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/9.meeting/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:51:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/9.meeting/index.html</guid>
      <description>Stakeholders meetings are crucial in ensuring a successful project, as it ensures alighnment among team members and the stakeholders. These meetings allows the team to have a proper understanding of the entire project. However, organizing and running effective stakeholder meetings requires careful planning and clear roles in order. The last thing a team wants is to leave an unprofessional impression, as this could damage trust and discourage stakeholders from continuing the collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G10 Virtual Production User Manual</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/user_manual/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 13:20:59 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/user_manual/index.html</guid>
      <description>Introduction This user manual consists of two parts:&#xA;User Manual for the Virtual Environment Asset – Instructions on opening and interacting with the virtual environment created by our team. User Manual for the Open Educational Resource (OER) – Guide on accessing the educational content provided. User Manual for Virtual Environment Asset 1. Introduction Welcome to the Virtual Environment Asset for Unreal Engine 5.3.3. This asset provides a high-quality, immersive environment for virtual production. It includes two distinct areas:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8: Preparation for Meeting with Stakeholders</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/8.preparation_for_meeting-with_stakeholders/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:31:59 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/8.preparation_for_meeting-with_stakeholders/index.html</guid>
      <description>After we won the bid for this project, we had a period of hiatus prior to formal contact with stakeholders. Because the stakeholders are busy, it is difficult to make appointments with them. So we had almost three weeks to prepare for formal contact. In the first week, we didn’t pay much attention to it, and that was our mistake. But after a meeting with our professor, Dave, we immediately realized the importance of meeting with stakeholders and started focusing on it right away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Engines</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/unreal-engine/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 17:28:24 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/unreal-engine/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>